{
    "subject": "Princess_Maria_Elisabeth_of_Bavaria",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Prince_Pedro_Henrique_of_Orl\u00e9ans-Braganza",
    "human_readable": "Princess Maria Elisabeth of Bavaria is married to Prince Pedro Henrique of Orl\u00e9ans-Braganza.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9887233972549438,
            "question": "Is there a marriage between Princess Maria Elisabeth of Bavaria and Prince Pedro Henrique of Orl\u00e9ans-Braganza?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9869426488876343,
            "question": "Who are the spouses in this pairing: Princess Maria Elisabeth of Bavaria and Prince Pedro Henrique of Orl\u00e9ans-Braganza?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9834772944450378,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Princess Maria Elisabeth of Bavaria and Prince Pedro Henrique of Orl\u00e9ans-Braganza?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9757775068283081,
            "question": "Who is Princess Maria Elisabeth of Bavaria married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9700314402580261,
            "question": "To whom is Prince Pedro Henrique of Orl\u00e9ans-Braganza married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9650802612304688,
            "question": "Is Prince Pedro Henrique of Orl\u00e9ans-Braganza married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9619607925415039,
            "question": "What is the full name of the person Prince Pedro Henrique of Orl\u00e9ans-Braganza is married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.940667450428009,
            "question": "Who is Princess Maria Elisabeth of Bavaria?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8056672811508179,
            "question": "What is the name of Princess Maria Elisabeth's husband?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7284322381019592,
            "question": "What title does Prince Pedro Henrique of Orl\u00e9ans-Braganza hold?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Princess Maria Elisabeth of Bavaria is married to Prince Pedro Henrique of Orl\u00e9ans-Braganza.",
            "html": "yago_31422_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Princess Maria Elisabeth's husband?",
            "html": "yago_31422_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Princess Maria Elisabeth of Bavaria?",
            "html": "yago_31422_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the full name of the person Prince Pedro Henrique of Orl\u00e9ans-Braganza is married to?",
            "html": "yago_31422_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31422_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31422_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31422_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31422_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31422_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31422_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31422_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31422_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31422_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31422_84.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "The triple \"Princess Maria Elisabeth of Bavaria is married to Prince Pedro Henrique of Orl\u00e9ans-Braganza\" can be evaluated as follows:\n\n* The documents mention that Princess Maria Elisabeth of Bavaria was born on September 14, 1914, and that she was the daughter of Prince Franz of Bavaria and Princess Isabella Antonie of Cro\u00ff.\n* One of the documents (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_31422/re-ranker-msmarco/38.txt) mentions that on August 19, 1937, Princess Maria Elisabeth married Pedro Henrique, Prince of Brazil, head of one of the branches of the Imperial House of Brazil.\n* Another document (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_31422/re-ranker-msmarco/16.txt) mentions that the wedding took place in the chapel of Nymphenburg Palace and lists several royal guests and relatives who were present at the wedding, including Pedro Henrique.\n* The documents do not mention any information that would contradict the statement that Princess Maria Elisabeth is married to Prince Pedro Henrique.\n\nTherefore, based on the provided context information:\n\n{ \"output\": \"yes\" }"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Princess Maria Elisabeth of Bavaria is married to Prince Pedro Henrique of Orl\u00e9ans-Braganza.\" Specific details include:\n\n- The marriage between Princess Maria Elisabeth of Bavaria and Pedro Henrique, Prince of Brazil (who was head of one of the branches of the Imperial House of Brazil) took place on 19 August 1937.\n- They had twelve children together and resided in Brazil until his death in 1981.\n- She passed away in 2011."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}